topcareer.jp 2018-10-22

# Privacy policy | Fourth Valley Concierge Corporation

#### Privacy Policy

Fourth Valley Concierge Corporation (hereinafter FVC) provides recruitment services for Top Global Talents, Global and domestic research, Translations/Interpretation services, and marketing support for Tourists to Japan.

FVC will establish a Privacy Policy in order to set a procedure for all our employees to appropriately handle personal information utilized for all our business, and will strictly adhere to this policy.

1\. FVC shall establish and appropriately operate a personal information management system based on the “Personal Information Protection Management System Requirements” (JISQ15001) to strictly adhere to the regulations stated by law and the country.

2\. FVC shall appropriately gather, utilize and provide personal information in consideration of the scope of its business and contents. This shall include the handling of personal information within the limits required to achieve the goals of its business and taking necessary measures required to achieve its goals.

3\. When entrusting all or partial handling of personal information, FVC shall appropriately supervise the entrusted for safe management of the information.

4\. FVC shall not provide the personal information to any third party unless agreed by the registrants/users or stated by laws.

5\. FVC shall take measures to prevent or improve divulging, loss, or damage of information.

6\. Registered personal information will be administrated by FVC, and will take all possible measures to manage the information. Requests for disclosure of personal information (communicating the purpose of use, disclosure, correction, addition, deletion of information, cancelation of service) shall be accepted. Please contact the below 【Complaints regards personal information and Consultation Desk】for procedures for disclosure.

7\. FVC shall continuously work on improvement of the personal information management system.  
thus may make changes to this policy from time to time. The changes to this policy will be posted here so be sure to check back periodically.

【Complaints regards personal information and Consultation Desk】  
Fourth Valley Concierge Corporation  
General Affairs department, General Affairs section  
TEL: 03-3263-6847  
FAX: 03-3263-6848  
E-mail: privacy@4th-valley.com  
(office hours Mondays to Fridays 10:00-16:00 excluding national holidays)

Enacted: June 1st, 2011  
Revised: June 1st, 2011  
Fourth Valley Concierge Corporation 

#### Handling of Personal Information at FVC

(Items for disclosures and those to keep in conditions easily accessed by individuals)

1\. Purpose of the usage of personal information

＜Purpose of usage of personal information subject for disclosure＞

(1) Information registered to the recruiting support HP  
・ To provide TOP CAREER Web related services, or to appropriately operate the various services by FVC

(2) Personal Information of the individual requesting for it  
・ to appropriately handle and manage information upon request

＜Purpose of the use of personal information other than in direct written document＞

(3) Personal information handled for business entrusted by client companies  
・ To appropriately conduct recruiting business entrusted by the client companies 

2\. Items to communicate regards personal information subject to disclosure

All purpose of use regards “personal information subject to disclosure” or for procedures of items such as “request of disclosure” and “items to communicate regards personal information subject to disclosure”, please contact 【Complaints regards personal information and Consultation Desk】. We shall be prompt in our replies.

【Complaints regards personal information and Consultation Desk】 Fourth Valley Concierge Corporation  
General Affairs department, General Affairs section  
TEL：03-3263-6847  
FAX：03-3263-6848  
e-mail：privacy@4th-valley.com  
(office hours Mondays to Fridays 10:00-16:00 excluding national holidays)
